drag\_handle

close

Privacy Policy
==============

Last Updated: 01/01/2022 (Version 1.1.1)

Cours Connecte Inc. - PRIVACY & COOKIE POLICY

Effective date: January 07th, 2018

Cours Connecte Inc., a corporation doing business under the name "Course Connect" (“Course Connect” “us”, “we”, or “our”) operates the [www.blckbx.ai](http://www.blckbx.ai/) and [www.useblackbox.io](http://www.useblackbox.io/) Site, Desktop Application, Browser Extension, Visual Studio Code Extension or API (the”Site, Desktop Application, Browser Extension, Visual Studio Code Extension or API”), allowing its users  to search the content of audio and video files.

This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use, disclosure and any other processing of personal data when you use our Site, Desktop Application, Browser Extension, Visual Studio Code Extension or API and the choices you have associated with that data.

We use your data to provide and improve the Site, Desktop Application, Browser Extension, Visual Studio Code Extension or API.

Whether you do so as an account holding user or as a guest, by either clicking to accept this Agreement or by accessing or using the Site, Desktop Application, Browser Extension, Visual Studio Code Extension or API, you acknowledge that you have read and understood this Agreement and agree to be bound by its terms.  If you are accepting this Agreement on behalf and in the name of a legal entity such as a company, corporation, partnership, etc. (referred to as a “Business”), you represent and warrant that you have the power and authority to bind such Business to this Agreement.  IF, HOWEVER, YOU ARE UNWILLING TO AGREE TO THIS AGREEMENT OR DO NOT HAVE THE POWER AND AUTHORITY TO ACT ON BEHALF OF AND BIND THE BUSINESS, YOU MUST NOT CLICK THAT YOU ACCEPT OR ACCESS OR USE THE SERVICE.

Definitions

“Personal Data” means any information relating to an identified or identifiable natural person; an identifiable natural person is one who can be identified, directly or indirectly, in particular by reference to an identifier such as a name, an identification number, location data, an online identifier or to one or more factors specific to the physical, physiological, genetic, mental, economic, cultural or social identity of that natural person.

“Cookies” are small pieces of data stored on a User’s device. They contain small amount of data which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a website and stored on your device.

“Data Controller” means the natural or legal person, public authority, agency or other body which, alone or jointly with others, determines the purposes and means of the processing of Personal Data.

For the purpose of this Privacy Policy, we are a Data Controller of your Personal Data.

“Data Processor” (or “Service Providers”) means a natural or legal person, public authority, agency or other body which processes Personal Data on behalf of the Data Controller (other than its own employees).

We may use the services of various Service Providers in order to process your data more effectively, all in accordance with this policy.

“Data Subject” means any natural person who is the subject of Personal Data. For the purpose of this privacy policy, you are the Data Subject.

“User” means the natural person using our Site, Desktop Application, Browser Extension, Visual Studio Code Extension or API. The User corresponds to the Data Subject, who is the subject of Personal Data.

Sources of Personal Data

We process the Personal Data that originated from the creation of your account and from your use of the Site, Desktop Application, Browser Extension, Visual Studio Code Extension or API, including the portion of the Site, Desktop Application, Browser Extension, Visual Studio Code Extension or API that requires the creation of an account to access.

Purposes of Processing and Legal Basis

Among the data we process, we process the following types of Personal Data for the following purposes to provide and improve our Site, Desktop Application, Browser Extension, Visual Studio Code Extension or API to you.

Account [Information.To](http://information.to/) use our Site, Desktop Application, Browser Extension, Visual Studio Code Extension or API, Users will need to create an account using their email address, full name and a password of their choice. Users may also elect to use our Site, Desktop Application, Browser Extension, Visual Studio Code Extension or API by connecting through their Gmail address and related password.

i.. We process each User’s email address, name and a password because the User needs to use them to sign in and connect to his/her account. The legal basis to this processing is our legitimate interest in protecting you account’s security.

We also process our Users’ email address to recognise them when they use our customer support. The legal basis for this processing is our legitimate interest in providing the best customer support we may offer you.

We also process our User’s email address for the purpose of sending them important information about the Site, Desktop Application, Browser Extension, Visual Studio Code Extension or API, such as important safety information or material changes to this policy. The legal basis to this processing is our legitimate interest in providing our Users with important safety or other important information regarding the Site, Desktop Application, Browser Extension, Visual Studio Code Extension or API or changes in this policy.

If you have consented to receiving marketing information from our part, we will also process your email address to send you such information about us or the Site, Desktop Application, Browser Extension, Visual Studio Code Extension or API. The legal basis to this processing is your consent. You may withdraw your consent at any time by changing your preferences in your account or by the unsubscribe link at the bottom of our marketing emails. The content of some of the marketing email you may receive from us is determined by your Cookies. The legal basis to this processing is our legitimate interest in reducing the number of marketing emails sent to our Users by automatically selecting content that may be more adapted to you instead of sending all our marketing emails to all our Users who has consented to receiving marketing emails.

Tracking Cookies Data.We process Cookies and similar tracking technologies such as beacons, tags, and scripts to track the activity on our Site, Desktop Application, Browser Extension, Visual Studio Code Extension or API and hold certain information to improve the Site, Desktop Application, Browser Extension, Visual Studio Code Extension or API and improve your overall experience when using the Site, Desktop Application, Browser Extension, Visual Studio Code Extension or API.

Examples of Cookies we use:

Session Cookies.We use Session Cookies to operate our Site.

Preference Cookies.We use Preference Cookies to remember your preferences and various settings.

Security Cookies.We use Security Cookies for security purposes.

i.If you have consented to the collect of information through the use of Cookies and similar tracking technologies, we will process Cookies and similar tracking technologies, with the assistance of third-party analytics services, to (i) analyse the way you navigate the Site (ii) generate statistics about the use of the Site, Desktop Application, Browser Extension, Visual Studio Code Extension or API, (iii) help diagnose problems with the Site, Desktop Application, Browser Extension, Visual Studio Code Extension or API and (iv) help administer the Site, Desktop Application, Browser Extension, Visual Studio Code Extension or API. The legal basis to this processing is our legitimate interest in providing to you the best experience on our Site, Desktop Application, Browser Extension, Visual Studio Code Extension or API.

If you delete your cookies, you will need to opt out again. There are browser plugins to help you preserve your-opt out cookies. For more information, please visit[http://www.aboutads.info/PMC](http://www.aboutads.info/PMC) or \[[https://youradchoices.ca/choices/protect-my-choices/.\](https://youradchoices.ca/choices/protect-my-choices/)](https://youradchoices.ca/choices/protect-my-choices/.%5D(https://youradchoices.ca/choices/protect-my-choices/))

Video Data and Text Data. We process the video and text data that you elect to search pursuant to the features available through the Site, Desktop Application, Browser Extension, Visual Studio Code Extension or API. You hereby certify that you have obtained, prior to processing and searching, the consent of all individuals which video and text data are to be processed and searched on the Site, Desktop Application, Browser Extension, Visual Studio Code Extension or API,  certify that you have obtained, prior to processing and searching, the consent of the owner of video and audio file,and that you will not process audio and video files of any person under the age of 18 years old. We also process the video data that has been transformed into text data. You acknowledge that you shall not process and search any sensitive data about any individual, including its racial origin or ethnicity, political opinions, religious or philosophical beliefs, trade union membership, biometrical data, medical data, and data regarding sexual activity or sexual orientation (“Sensitive Data”). The Site, Desktop Application, Browser Extension, Visual Studio Code Extension or API shall in no way be used to process and search, collect or store Sensitive Data.

i.. We process video data and text data in order to render the services provided through the Site, Desktop Application, Browser Extension, Visual Studio Code Extension or API, namely to allow you  to process and search the content of audio and video files.

The legal basis for this processing is the execution of the agreement between you and Course Connect regarding the use of the Site, Desktop Application, Browser Extension, Visual Studio Code Extension or API pursuant to our Terms and conditions and this Privacy and cookie policy.

Geolocation Data. We may collect and process information about your location. We use this information to optimize your experience on the Site, Desktop Application, Browser Extension, Visual Studio Code Extension or API. In order to determine your position, we will take into account, in particular, the geolocation data and any other necessary means.

i.The legal basis to this processing is our legitimate interest in providing to you the best experience on our Site, Desktop Application, Browser Extension, Visual Studio Code Extension or API.

Retention of Personal Data

COURSE CONNECT will retain your Personal Data for the duration of your continued access to the Site, Desktop Application, Browser Extension, Visual Studio Code Extension or API and for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy. We will retain and use your Personal Data to the extent necessary to comply with our legal obligations (for example, if we are required to retain your data to comply with applicable laws), resolve disputes, and enforce our legal agreements and policies, but no later.

Processing of Personal Data in the United-States

We process your Personal Data on our systems in the United-States. Therefore, your information, including Personal Data, may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ than those from your jurisdiction.

Accordingly, if you are located outside the United-States and choose to provide information to us, know that your Personal Data will be processed there.

Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to the processing in the United-States.

COURSE CONNECT will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy and no transfer of your Personal Data will take place to an organization or a country unless there are adequate controls in place including the security of your Personal Data. For any transfer of Personal Data to a jurisdiction that is not automatically considered as an adequate jurisdiction for a transfer of your Personal Data without additional requirement, all steps necessary to satisfy those requirements are taken by us, such as using Model Contractual Clause, for the European Union.

Disclosure of Personal Data

Business Transaction

If COURSE CONNECT is involved in a merger, acquisition or asset sale, your Personal Data may be transferred if the assignee is compliant with all legislations regarding Personal Data that apply to you and is taking the same or better means to protect your Personal Data than our. We will provide notice before your Personal Data is transferred and becomes subject to a different Privacy Policy.

Disclosure for Law Enforcement

Under certain circumstances, COURSE CONNECT may be required to disclose your Personal Data if required to do so by law or in response to valid requests by public authorities (e.g. a court or a government agency).

Legal Requirements

COURSE CONNECTE may disclose your Personal Data in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to:

To comply with a legal obligation

To protect and defend the rights or property of COURSE CONNECT

To prevent or investigate possible wrongdoing in connection with the Site, Desktop Application, Browser Extension, Visual Studio Code Extension or API To protect the personal safety of users of the Site, Desktop Application, Browser Extension, Visual Studio Code Extension or API or the public

To protect against legal liability

Security of Data

The security of your Personal Data is important to us but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Data, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

Nevertheless, we are providing you with updated measures of protection and physical, electronic and operational security, pursuant to the best standards and practices of the industry.

Your Rights

COURSE CONNECT aims to take reasonable steps to allow you to correct, amend, delete, limit or oppose to the process of your Personal Data.

Whenever made possible, you can update your Personal Data directly within your account settings section. If you are unable to change your Personal Data, please contact us to make the required changes.

If you wish to be informed what Personal Data we hold about you and if you want it to be removed from our systems, please contact us. However, you may at any time withdraw any consent you gave us to process your Personal Data in the preference settings of your account. In this case, we will, as soon as commercially and reasonably possible, delete from our systems all your Personal Data obtained on the legal basis of your consent and request our processors to do the same. By doing so, please be aware that you may not access all of the features of the Site, Desktop Application, Browser Extension, Visual Studio Code Extension or API.

Without limiting the foregoing, in certain circumstances, you have the right:

To access and receive a copy of the Personal Data we hold about you

To rectify any Personal Data held about you that is inaccurate

To request the deletion of Personal Data held about you

You also have the right to data portability for the information you provide to COURSE CONNECT. You have the right to receive your Personal Data in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format and have the right to transmit those data to another controller without hindrance from us or the controller to which your Personal Data have been provided. You have the right to have your Personal Data transmitted directly from us or the controller to another controller, where technically feasible.

Depending of your jurisdiction (ex. Canada and European Union), you may have the right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority.

Please note that we may ask you to verify your identity before responding to such requests.

Recipients or Categories of Recipients of Personal Data

We may employ third party Services providers and individuals to facilitate our Service, to provide the Site, Desktop Application, Browser Extension, Visual Studio Code Extension or API on our behalf, to perform Site, Desktop Application, Browser Extension, Visual Studio Code Extension or API -related services or to assist us in analyzing how our Site, Desktop Application, Browser Extension, Visual Studio Code Extension or API is used.

These third parties have access to your Personal Data only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.

Analytics. We may use third-party Service Providers to monitor and analyze the use of our Site, Desktop Application, Browser Extension, Visual Studio Code Extension or API.

Links to Other Sites

Our Site, Desktop Application, Browser Extension, Visual Studio Code Extension or API may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third-party link, you will be directed to that third party's site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.

We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third-party sites or services.

Children's Privacy

Our Site, Desktop Application, Browser Extension, Visual Studio Code Extension or API does not address anyone under the age of 16 ("Children").

We do not knowingly collect Personal Data from anyone under the age of 16. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your Children have provided us with Personal Data, please contact us. If we become aware that we have collected Personal Data from children without verification of parental consent, we take steps to remove that information from our servers.

Changes to This Privacy Policy

We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.

We will let you know via email and/or a prominent notice on our Site, prior to the change becoming effective and update the "effective date" at the top of this Privacy Policy.

You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact the Personal Data Management Coordinator:

Course Connect inc.

Personal Data Management Coordinator

Robert Rizk

Email: [blackboxapp@blackboxai.tech](mailto:blackboxapp@blackboxai.tech)

Copyright © Course Connect inc. All rights reserved.
